Finding Aid for the Yale Reports Transcripts PASC.0231
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Paul Hindemith: Life and Music at Yale, 12/27/1964 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  Number: 343
- Peking's Cultural Revolution I: The Background, 10/9/1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Number: 406
- Peking's Cultural Revolution II: The Characteristics, 10/16/1966 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Number: 407
- Peking's Cultural Revolution III: The Causes, 10/23/1966 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Number: 408
- A Perfection of Utopias, 11/29/1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Number: 570
- PHILOSOPHIES OF TODAY IV: LOGIC, 3/29/1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Number: 147
- PHILOSOPHIES OF TODAY V: POLITICAL PHILOSOPHY, 4/5/1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Number: 148
- PHILOSOPHIES OF TODAY VI: METAPHYSICS, 4/12/1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Number: 149
- PHILOSOPHIES OF TODAY I: JOHN DEWEY AND AMERICAN PRAGMATISM, 3/8/1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Number: 144
- PHILOSOPHIES OF TODAY II: EXISTENTIAL PHILOSOPHY, 3/15/1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Number: 145
- PHILOSOPHIES OF TODAY III: ANALYTIC PHILOSOPHY, 3/22/1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Number: 146
- Physical Mobility and Social Choice, 2/2/1969 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  Number: 501
- PLACE OF PSYCHIATRY IN THE MODERN WORLD I: WHAT IS PSYCHIATRY? (The), 9/21/1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Number: 121
- PLACE OF PSYCHIATRY IN THE MODERN WORLD II: PSYCHIATRY IN THE HOSPITAL (The), 9/28/1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Number: 122
- PLACE OF PSYCHIATRY IN THE MODERN WORLD IV: CHILD PSYCHIATRY (The), 10/12/1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Number: 123
- PLACE OF PSYCHIATRY IN THE MODERN WORLD V: THE FUTURE, 10/19/1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Number: 124
- Plays and Playwrights, 4/7/1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Number: 284
- A Playwright Looks At the Theater Today, 6/5/1966 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Number: 402
- Poetic Choices of Helen Chasin (The), 6/23/1968 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Number: 482
- A Political Dialogue, 4/28/1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Number: 287
- A Political Philosophy, 6/2/1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Number: 292
- A Political Stage, 6/22/1969 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  Number: 521
- Political and Military Strategy in Latin America, 3/1/1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Number: 315
- Politics in America: The California Experience, 1/13/1963 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  Number: 272
- Politics In America: The Modern Presidency - I, 2/10/1963 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  Number: 276
- Politics In America: The Modern Presidency - II, 2/17/1963 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  Number: 277
- Politics of Defense Dollars (The), 10/4/1970 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  Number: 562
- Polycentrism in the Soviet Bloc, 6/7/1964 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Number: 329
- Portrait of an Artist, 1/12/1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Number: 308
- Position of a Southern Governor, 12/6/1964 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  Number: 340
- Possibilities of Stability in the New Africa, 12/3/1967 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  Number: 453
- Problems in Africa III: Problems of Personnel Research in Africa, 1/8/1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Number: 212
- Problems of Conviction and Arrest, 1/29/1967 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  Number: 422
- Problems of Poverty, 5/15/1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Number: 399
- Professor as a Composer (The), 12/16/1962 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  Number: 268
- Professor as a Poet (The), 12/9/1962 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  Number: 267
- Propaganda and the United Nations, 11/14/1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Number: 373
- PSYCHIATRY IN THE MODERN WORLD III: PSCHIATRY AND THE COMMUNITY, 10/5/1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- PSYCHOLOGY AND SOVIET EDUCATION I: SOVIET PSYCHOLOGY TODAY, 2/1/1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Number: 139
- PSYCHOLOGY AND SOVIET EDUCATION II: SOVIET PSYCHOLOGY AS RELATED TO SOVIET EDUCATION, 2/8/1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Number: 140
- Psychology, Presidents and Political Scientists, 11/30/1969 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  Number: 531
- Public Employees and the Law: Part I, 2/23/1969 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  Number: 504
- Public Employees and the Law: Part II, 3/2/1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Number: 505
- Putting Maps on the Map, 4/23/1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Number: 227
- Pyramid Climbers (The), 3/3/1963 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  Number: 279
- Ralph McGill: A Journalist, A Southerner, 5/1/1966 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Number: 397
- Real Life of Myths (The), 6/16/1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Number: 481
- Recent French Policies Under DeGaulle, 5/8/1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Number: 398
- Reflections on Higher Education, 5/3/1964 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Number: 324
- Remaking of a Nation: Malaysia 1964 (The), 12/13/1964 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  Number: 341
- Renaissance and Baroque Music, 11/3/1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Number: 299
- Renewal, Roman Catholicism, and the Third Man, 1/19/1969 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Number: 499
- Reporting the War In Vietnam, 5/19/1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Number: 477
- Responsible Nuclear Policy, 3/17/1963 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  Number: 281
- Responsible Scientist, Part II, Chemical and Biological Warfare (The), 11/16/1969 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  Number: 529
- Responsible Scientist: Part III, Shaping National Scientific Policy (The), 11/22/1969 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  Number: 530
- Responsible Scientist: Part One, Our Brother's Brother (The), 11/9/1969 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  Number: 528
- Rhetoric of the New Left (The), 4/21/1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Number: 473
- Richard Wilbur: Candide, Loudmouse and the Undead, 4/20/1969 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  Number: 512
- Role of a Literary Critic (The), 3/31/1963 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  Number: 283
- ROLE OF AMERICA'S LOYAL OPPOSITION (The), 5/3/1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Number: 152
- Role of Government in the Arts - II (The), 6/3/1962 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  Number: 257
- ROLE OF THE CITIZEN IN POLITICS I: DOES THE CITIZEN HAVE A SAY IN POLITICS? (The), 10/23/1960 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  Number: 201
- ROLE OF THE CITIZEN IN POLITICS II (The), 10/30/1960 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  Number: 202
- ROLE OF THE CITIZEN IN POLITICS III: THE FUNCTION OF THE PRESIDENCY (The), 11/6/1960 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  Number: 203
- Russia and the World I: The Popular Images Russian View of the West and Western View of Russia, 5/21/1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Number: 231
- Russia and the World II: Official Images Government's View of East and West, 5/28/1961 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Number: 232
- Russia and the World III: Ideology, Theory and Political Reality, 6/4/1961 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Number: 233
- Russia From Stalin to Khrushchev, 10/6/1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Number: 295
- Russian Chorus (The), 11/11/1962 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  Number: 263
- Satirist and the Senior Class: Dick Gregory at Yale (The), 1/14/1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Number: 459
- Saying the Unthinkable, 1/2/1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Number: 380
- Saying the Unthinkable II, 1/9/1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Number: 381
- Scholars View the World - I: Africa, 3/4/1962 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  Number: 244
- Scholars View the World - II: Latin America, 3/11/1962 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  Number: 245
- Scholars View the World - III: The Middle East, 3/18/1962 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Number: 246
- Scholars View the World - IV: Canada and the British Commonwealth, 3/25/1962 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Number: 247
- Search For Extraterrestrial Life (The), 3/28/1965 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  Number: 356
- Selecting Freshmen: The Awesome Task of American Colleges, 10/2/1966 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Number: 405
- Should Mathematicians Be Shot At 30, and Other Questions of Specialized Education, 10/22/1967 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  Number: 447
- SHOULD UNIVERSITIES CONDUCT DEFENSE STUDIES?, 5/15/1960 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  Number: 192
- Singapore: The Israel of Asia?, 6/9/1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Number: 480
- Socialism in a New Setting, 1/10/1965 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  Number: 345
- SOME IMPRESSIONS OF THE FAR EAST I: A YEAR IN THE FAR EAST, 1/3/1960 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  Number: 173
- Speculations, 4/19/1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Number: 551
- State of the Economy I: The Forecast, 2/12/1967 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  Number: 424
- State of the Economy II: Policies For Stability, 2/19/1967 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  Number: 425
- State of the Economy III: Program Priorities, 2/26/1967 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  Number: 426
- Staying Alive Part I: Problems of Human Ecology, 12/1/1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Number: 492
- Staying Alive, Part II: Man and His Cities, 12/8/1968 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Number: 493
- Staying Alive: Part III, Stress Aspects of Today's Life Styles, 12/15/1968 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  Number: 494
- Student Activities in the South: Inspiration or Interference?, 10/3/1965 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  Number: 367
- Symphonies: Drew, 12/29/1968 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Number: 496
- Theatre: Amenity or Necessity?, 5/15/1966 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Number: 400
- Thinking About Writing About Women, 5/4/1969 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  Number: 514
- A Toscanini Centennial: Part I, 1/21/1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Number: 460
- A Toscanini Centennial: Part II, 1/28/1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Number: 461
- Tripping Out: Designing Mass Transit, 2/21/1971 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  Number: 582
- Twenties and After: Vintage Years of American Literature (The), 1/1/1967 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  Number: 418
- Two Decades of Peking Foreign Policy, 4/26/1970 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Number: 552
- Two Views of Congress I: The House, 3/12/1967 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  Number: 428
- Two Views of Congress II: The Senate, 3/19/1967 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  Number: 429
- Undergraduates Abroad: Testing Classroom Knowledge, 1/8/1967 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Number: 419
- Unions, Management, and the Public - I: The Role of Government in Collective Bargaining, 4/1/1962 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  Number: 248
- Unions, Management, and the Public - II: The Future of Unionism in the U.S., 4/8/1962 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  Number: 249
- Unions, Management, and the Public - III: Automation, 4/15/1962 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  Number: 250
- Universities for Export, 5/7/1961 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Number: 229
- University and National Government (The), 4/12/1964 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  Number: 321
- University and Revolution (The), 5/18/1969 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  Number: 516
- UNIVERSITY AS PUBLISHER I: WHAT IS SCHOLARLY PUBLISHING?, 6/11/1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Number: 118
- UNIVERSITY AS PUBLISHER II: THE SCHOLAR AND THE UNIVERSITY PRESS (The), 6/22/1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Number: 119
- UNIVERSITY AS PUBLISHER III: THE FUTURE OF SCHOLARLY PUBLISHING (The), 6/29/1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Number: 120
- An Unorthodox Look at Smoking, 4/4/1965 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  Number: 357
- Up the Leaning Tower of Jello: Making Cable Communications Work, 3/14/1971 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  Number: 584
- Utopias, 6/6/1965 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  Number: 366
- Vatican II and Church Renewal: Quo Vadis?, 2/28/1965 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  Number: 352
- A Veteran Correspondent's View of America's Image Abroad, 1/15/1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Number: 213
- Vietnam at Yale, 5/30/1965 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  Number: 365
- A View From the Hill, 3/21/1965 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  Number: 355
- Vinland Map Discovery, 11/21/1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Number: 374
- Violence Inside the Brain, 3/23/1969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  Number: 508
- What About England? Economic and Political Perspectives, 12/10/1967 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  Number: 454
- What Is Biafra?, 3/31/1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Number: 470
- WHAT IS HAPPENING IN SECONDARY EDUCATION I: WHAT IS HAPPENING IN THE HIGH SCHOOLS, 3/27/1960 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  Number: 185
- WHAT IS HAPPENING IN SECONDARY EDUCATION II: WHAT IS HAPPENING IN TEACHER TRAINING, 4/4/1960 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  Number: 186
- WHAT IS HAPPENING IN SECONDARY EDUCATION III: CAN SCHOOLS TEACH VALUES?, 4/10/1960 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  Number: 187
- WHAT IS HAPPENING IN SECONDARY EDUCATION IV: THE TRUE PURPOSES OF EDUCATION, 4/17/1960 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  Number: 188
- What Is History?, 11/15/1964 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  Number: 337
- What Is REM Sleep?, 4/5/1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Number: 549
- When the Two of Us Are Talking, 1/25/1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Number: 539
- Who gets the Peace Dividend?, 10/5/1969 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  Number: 523
- Who Runs Big City Schools?, 5/21/1967 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  Number: 438
- Why No Federation For Central Africa?, 5/14/1961 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Number: 230
- Will the Suburbs Take Over?, 5/31/1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Number: 557
- Witches, Demons, and Other Fly-By-Nights, 12/7/1969 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  Number: 532
- Women, the Law and the Abortion Issue, 4/13/1969 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  Number: 511
- WORK OF A LITERARY DETECTIVE (The), 10/16/1960 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  Number: 200
- WORLD AND PUBLIC HEALTH (The), 1/10/1960 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Number: 174
- WORLD ECONOMY I: THE PLANNED ECONOMY OF THE SOVIET UNION, 11/15/1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  Number: 166
- WORLD ECONOMY II: THE ECONOMY OF THE UNITED STATES TODAY, 11/22/1959 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Number: 167
- WORLD ECONOMY III: THE ECONOMY OF THE UNCOMMITTED NATIONS, 11/29/1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Number: 168
- Writers on Writing - I, 2/11/1962 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Number: 241
- Writers on Writing - II, 2/18/1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Number: 242
- Writers on Writing - III, 2/25/1962 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Number: 243
- YALE SCHOLARS AND STUDENTS BEHIND THE IRON CURTAIN I: TITO'S YUGOSLAVIA, 10/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Number: 125
- Yale Series of Recorded Poets I: The Value of Poetry Recordings, 1/22/1961 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Number: 214
- Yale Series of Recorded Poets II: Poets as Readers of Their Own Work, 1/29/1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Number: 215
- Yale Series of Recorded Poets III: Appraisal of Young Anglo-American Poetry, 2/5/1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Number: 216
- Youth, Law and Order, 10/6/1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Number: 484